(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Well, you know, just...
(sniffs)
(Leonard:)being myself, really.
Oh, please!
(Sheldon:)You know, I'll tell you
how he did it.
(Sheldon:)Implacable,
relentless badgering.
(Sheldon:)In urology terms,
(Sheldon:)he was a drug-resistant
staph infection.
(Sheldon:)And she was a urethra
that could not shake him.
(Leonard:)I don't know that I'd call
myself an infection.
(Howard:)A gallant man would
defend his fiancée
(Howard:)for being called a urethra.
(Leonard:)Can we please
change the subject?
(Amy:)Hi.
(Raj:)Well, that didn't
go your way.
(Penny:)Dr. Lorvis,
what are you doing here?
(Dr Lorvis:)Uh, well, actually
I came to see you.
(Penny:)Really? Why?
(Leonard:)Ah, that's a good question.
(Leonard:)Apparently someone was
being awfully flirty
(Leonard:)while not wearing
their engagement ring,
(Leonard:)causing another
someone to show up
(Leonard:)here thinking the first
someone might be available.